justsnipe.com 2008-06-15

# Privacy Policy at JustSnipe: We provide online auction sniping application.

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for JustSnipe.com and its owner JUSTCUTE INC. 

Information Usage and Collection:   
JustSnipe and JUSTCUTE INC. are the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. We collect information from our users at several different points on our website.

Registration:   
In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information and other unique identifiers, but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. Some financial information is required in order to process with the payment processing system. 

Cookies:   
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie in our site is for the purpose of maintaining the session of an individual user. Some business partners may have used cookies, however, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

Links:   
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we (JustSnipe) are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

Notification of Changes:   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.   

If you have any questions regarding about the policy, please contact [support@justsnipe.com](mailto:support@justsnipe.com)
